I'd go to the moon just
to get close to you
But sitting in your room I
feel so far far far away
You know what to do to
pull me into you
Cuz every time you move you take
my breath breath breath away
When I hear you
Suddenly off my feet
So baby come through, I'll
play you on repeat
You're singing a sad song, but
you make it sound happy
You got the perfect words to
hurt me so hurt me so good
You're singing a sad song, but
you make it sound happy
You're playing my heart
& I'm falling apart
Just like I knew I would
Tell me why I save every
last dance for you
And everything you say I
memori-i-i-ize it all
You know how to get me higher
Even when I wanna cry
But you're setting me on fire
just to wa-wa-warm you up
When I hear you
Suddenly off my feet
So baby come through, I'll
play you on repeat
You're singing a sad song, but
you make it sound happy
You got the perfect words to
hurt me so hurt me so good
You're singing a sad song, but
you make it sound happy
You're playing my heart
& I'm falling apart
Just like I knew I would
Hear you deep inside of me
Your back and forth is
slowly ******* me
Don't just leave me quietly
Play your song and keep convincing me
You're singing a sad song, but
you make it sound happy
You got the perfect words to
hurt me so hurt me so good
You're singing a sad song, but
you make it sound happy
You're playing my heart
& I'm falling apart
Just like I knew I would